<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
        <pizza name="Margherita">
            <ingridient name="flour">330g</ingridient>

            <ingridient name ="salt">1 tsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "yeast">1 tbsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="olive oil">1 tbsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="water">200 ml</ingridient>



            <ingridient name="tomato paste">100 ml</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "garlic">1 clove</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "bazil">1 tbsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "mozarella">250g</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "cherry tomatoes">1 glass</ingridient>


            <instruction>
                Make the basis. To do this, take a large bowl and add flour, yeast and salt. We mix well, and then we pour water (warm room temperature) and olive oil into the mixture. Again we stir it to a uniform mass.

                We will transfer the dough on the pre-sprinkled flour, laid out on the table confectionery paper. And crushed for 5 minutes.

                After covering with a towel and leave aside to raise the dough. Although this item is not mandatory. If you need a thin crust, you can immediately start the next step.

                Now we make a sauce for pizza «Margarita». We mix all the ingredients: paste, basil, garlic. We’ll leave it at room temperature while we prepare the base.

                If you did not give the opportunity to climb the dough, then immediately roll. In any case, do a rolling circle of 25 cm - 30 cm in diameter. The dough should be thin as it will rise in the oven.

                Prepare the filling - the basic composition. Preheat the oven to 220-240 degrees. Place an oven on the top shelf, you can even turn it over.

                Spread the sauce on the dough back (convex) part of the spoon over the entire surface. Scatter grated or sliced cheese and tomatoes. Sprinkle with olive oil and seasoning.

                Place the dough tray on the heated pan in the oven. Bake for 8-10 minutes to crisp.
            </instruction>
        </pizza>

        <pizza name="Pepperoni">
            <ingridient name="flour">330g</ingridient>

            <ingridient name ="salt">1 tsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name = "yeast">1 tbsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="olive oil">1 tbsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="water">200 ml</ingridient>



            <ingridient name="tomato paste">100 ml</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="garlic">1 clove</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="bazil">1 tsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="mozarella">250 g</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="salami">200 g</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="canned tomatoes">1 can</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="black pepper">to taste</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="oregano">1 tsp</ingridient>

            <ingridient name="chilli pepper">1 pc</ingridient>

            <instructuion>
                First, make the sauce: mix tomatoes with spices, crushed garlic, sugar, salt and pepper.

                Bring it to a boil and cool it.

                Roll the dough, grease it with olive oil and sauce.

                Sprinkle half the cheese, lay out the sausage and thin sliced chili.

                On top is the remaining cheese.
                Cook in the oven for 10-12 minutes at 220 degrees.
            </instructuion>
        </pizza>
</root>